Guide to the Jacques E. Levy Research Collection on Cesar Chavez
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Miscellaneous Cesar Chavez Tape Collection, 1969-1976; Series II; 0.67; (5 boxes)
  - AUDIOTAPES
    - Tape 46. JEL interviewed on KUHL, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368509)
    - Tape 47. KGO's Jim Esson with priest and JEL call in, undated; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368517)
    - Tape 48. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (1 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368525)
    - Tape 49. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (2 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368533)
    - Tape 50. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (3 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368541)
    - Tape 51. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (4 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002099368558)
    - Tape 52. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (5 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104885729)
    - Tape 53. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (6 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104885737)
    - Tape 54. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (7 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104885745)
    - Tape 55. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (8 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104885752)
    - Tape 56. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (9 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104885760)
    - Tape 57. JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez (10 of 10 audiocassettes), 1974 July 20-22; 1 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104885778)
  - TRANSCRIPTS
    - File 1. Helen Chavez in Salinas and JEL notes (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - File 2. Ethel Kennedy in Salinas, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - File 3. Cesar Chavez re manuscript, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 258)
      Two copies of transcript
- Jacques E. Levy's Notebook Collection, 1968-1994; Series III; 3.15; (9 boxes)
  Series III, Jacques E. Levy's Notebook Collection, contains the author's original field notes, which are organized in chronological order from 1968-1994.
  - 1968-1969
    - Notebook 1. Pre-book research on numerous subjects and early interviews with Chavez, 1968-69 (Box 8, Folder 259)
    - Notebook 2. Various notes and questions for Cesar Chavez. Also short early drafts for book, [Early 1969] (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - Notebook 3. Early drafts for first part of book, [Early 1969] (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - Notebook 4. Miscellaneous notes, [Early 1969] (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - Notebook 5. JEL notes re People for a Better Society actions pending in Santa Rosa. Back of book: JEL scribbles for book title and attempts at several passages, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 263)
    - Notebook 6. Interviews with Cruz Reynoso, Kevin Keene Larson, Mrs. Kathy Murguia, review and plans by Fred Ross, Larry Itliong interview, interview with Chavez. Back of book: Fred Ross interview, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - Notebook 7. Notes taken from Wayne State Walter Reuther Labor Library Collection on farm workers union, interview with Hijnio Rangel, organizing material for first draft dealing with Chavez childhood. Back of book: Library notes. Midbook: half page of Chavez interview, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - 1970
    - Notebook 8. Notes on PBS activities, list of questions for Father Donald McDonnell, 1970 Jan (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - Notebook 9. List of questions for Cesar Chavez, Levy arguments for writing book in first person, Chavez interview. Back of book: Chavez interview, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 267)
    - Notebook 10. Notes on activities during grape strike, negotiations, 1970 Jun-Jul (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - Notebook 11. Notes on current events, questions for Chavez, background notes on Marshall Ganz and LeRoy Chatfield. Back of book: notes on grape strike negotiations and Chavez reactions, 1970 Jul (Box 8, Folder 269)
    - Notebook 12. Unidentified person's notes including a treasurer's report. Back of book: Miscellaneous Levy notes on Salinas, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 270)
      Includes typescript note laid in loose at back tendering Sally Lopez's resignation from the MAPA Organization
    - Notebook 13. More notes on strike. Back of book: Details of events in Watsonville and other parts of California re strikes, 1970 Jul-Aug (Box 9, Folder 271)
    - Notebook 14. Notes of union's negotiations with major Delano growers, 1970 Jul 16-28 (Box 9, Folder 272)
    - Notebook 15. Negotiations with United Fruit and other growers in August 1970, 1970 Aug 12-22 (Box 9, Folder 273)
    - Notebook 16. Negotiations with United Fruit and other growers in August 1970 cont., 1970 Aug 22-30 (Box 9, Folder 274)
    - Notebook 17. Chavez participation in negotiations with United Fruit and other growers in August 1970, 1970 Aug 14-31 (Box 9, Folder 275)
    - Notebook 18. Negotiations with United Fruit in August and September 1970, 1970 Aug-Sep (Box 9, Folder 276)
    - Notebook 19. Negotiations with United Fruit, Chavez prison statement, 1970 Sep-Dec (Box 9, Folder 277)
    - Notebook 20. Notes on Chavez trial, interview of Jerry Cohen, other notes of activities, 1970 Sep-Dec (Box 9, Folder 278)
    - Notebook 21. Day to day diary of events, 1970 Sep-Dec (Box 9, Folder 279)
    - Notebook 22. Notes from Dolores Huerta about contact with Chavez, 1970 Oct 8 (Box 9, Folder 280)
    - Notebook 23. Notes, press conference of religious leaders, 1970 Dec (Box 9, Folder 281)
  - 1971
    - Notebook 24. Miscellaneous notes, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 282)
    - Notebook 25. Miscellaneous notes, most on Levy peace activities, a few regarding farm workers, 1971 Feb-Apr (Box 9, Folder 283)
    - Notebook 26. Notes on 2/4/71 court hearing. Jerry Cohen interview. Back of book: Notes on talk by anti-labor management relations official, questions for Chavez, 1971 Feb-May (Box 10, Folder 284)
    - Notebook 27. List of questions re Levy manuscript. Notes on George Meany attacking Chavez in Miami and Kircher defending Chavez, 1970-71 (Box 10, Folder 285)
    - Notebook 28. Notes on negotiations between vegetable growers and union. Reactions of grower attorney Church and Fleming, Chavez stories, 1971 May-Jun (Box 10, Folder 286)
    - Notebook 29. Questions for Lionel Steinberg, notes on interview, 1971 Jun (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - Notebook 30. Interview with Lionel Steinberg. Negotiations with lettuce growers, 1971 Jun-Aug (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - Notebook 31. Various notes from the field. Notes on Larry Itliong resigning from union, 1971 Jul-Aug (Box 10, Folder 289)
    - Notebook 32. List of pages of Levy notes, organizing them for first draft of book. Back of book: Notes on plot against Chavez, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 290)
    - Notebook 33. Notes on contents of tapes made by Larry Shears, notes on plot investigation, 1971-72 (Box 10, Folder 291)
    - Notebook 34. Notes on assassination plot, trials, 1971-72 (Box 10, Folder 292)
      Accompanied by sheet of typescript and holograph questions for Jim Christiensen laid in loose
    - Notebook 35. Negotiations with lettuce growers, notes on California McGovern delegation to National Democratic Convention, notes on assassination plot, notes on agreement with Rolling Stone, 1971-72 (Box 10, Folder 293)
  - 1972
    - Notebook 36. Notes of Levy activities in Sonoma County, Chavez dog problems. Back of book: Notes setting up union paper, notes on boycott, 1972 Jan-Mar (Box 10, Folder 294)
    - Notebooks 37-38. Notes on assassination plot against Chavez, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 295-296)
    - Notebook 39. Notes on assassination plot, meeting with FBI, 1972 Feb 15 (Box 11, Folder 297)
    - Notebook 40. Notes on lie detector tests given Larry Shears, interviews with ATF agents and other law enforcement, 1972, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - Notebook 41. Notes regarding assassination plot accomplices, Lipset, law enforcement agencies including ATF, 1972 May 9 (Box 11, Folder 299)
    - Notebook 42. Arizona fast and union's actions to recall Arizona governor, 1972 May-Jun (Box 11, Folder 300)
    - Notebook 43. Investigation of assassination plot, 1972 Jun (Box 11, Folder 301)
    - Notebook 44. California delegation at Democratic National Convention, miscellaneous notes, 1972 Jul (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - 1973
    - Notebook 45. Notes on Hells Angel trial, meetings with Chavez, dealing with manuscript for book, 1973 Jan-Mar (Box 11, Folder 303)
    - Notebook 46. Notes organizing material for book, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 304)
    - Notebook 47. Notes made at scene of mass arrests and other events, 1973 Apr (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Notebook 48. Report on union by Chavez, activities and press conferences, 1973 Apr 15-27 (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - Notebook 49. Strategy notes, notes while traveling with Chavez, secret meetings with AFL-CIO leaders, 1973 Apr-Jul (Box 12, Folder 307)
    - Notebook 50. Notes on union constitution, events, 1973 Apr-Aug (Box 12, Folder 308)
    - Notebook 51. Notes on violence and boycott, 1973 Jun 7-13 (Box 12, Folder 309)
    - Notebook 52. Notes on press conference held by Chavez, court hearing, testing of grapes for sugar content, violence in Coachella Valley, 1973 Jun (Box 12, Folder 310)
    - Notebook 53. Reports of Teamster violence, interviews with farm workers, daily notes. Back of book: brief note on Robert Mardian, 1973 Jun-Jul (Box 12, Folder 311)
    - Notebook 54. Reports of grape sugar content, complaints sent concerning assassination plot case, copy of Teamsters' account of law violations, 1973 Jul (Box 12, Folder 312)
    - Notebook 55. Notes of current events, rally in Delano, 1973 Jul-Aug (Box 12, Folder 313)
    - Notebook 56. Notes on meeting with Delano growers, and assassination plot, 1973 Jul-Aug (Box 12, Folder 314)
    - Notebook 57. Reports from Richard Chavez on support for boycott, violence on picket lines, Fresno courthouse demonstration, notes on death of Nagi Daifullah and Juan De La Cruz, 1973 Aug 2-21 (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - Notebook 58. Notes on negotiations, reports of violence, Chavez press conference, 1973 Aug-Sep (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - Notebook 59. Notes on violence and union list of grievances, 1973 Aug-Sep (Box 12, Folder 317)
    - Notebook 60. UFW convention, notes on assassination plot, 1973 Sep-Oct (Box 13, Folder 318)
    - Notebook 61. Notes on assassination plot, UFW convention, 1973 Sep 25 (Box 13, Folder 319)
    - Notebook 62. Notes on JEL finances, calls to and from Chavez concerning boycott, 1973 Oct (Box 13, Folder 320)
    - Notebook 63. Back of book: various notes and questions, 1973 Nov (Box 13, Folder 321)
    - Notebook 64. UFW executive board meeting, interview with ATF agent, 1973 Dec (Box 13, Folder 322)
  - 1974
    - Notebook 65. Brief notes, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 323)
    - Notebook 66. Various working notes, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 324)
    - Notebook 67. Notes on relations between union and AFL-CIO, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 325)
    - Notebook 68. Miscellaneous notes, mostly by others in Santa Rosa, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 326)
    - Notebook 69. Travel information for Europe trip, notes on Gallo strike, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 327)
    - Notebook 70. Editing notes for book, notes on assassination plot, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 328)
    - Notebook 71. Miscellaneous notes. Back of book: notes on UFW history, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 329)
    - Notebook 72. Details of Chavez going after border patrol, lots of notes on farm labor laws and legislative hearings, dedication of Paulo Agbayani Village in Delano, union board meeting, 1974 May-Jun (Box 14, Folder 330)
  - 1975
    - Notebook 73. Notes on school board candidates night, California Labor Relations Act, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 331)
    - Notebook 74. Notes on California Legislature committee hearings on Agricultural Labor Relations Act, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 332)
    - Notebook 75. Senate committee hearings, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 333)
    - Notebook 76. Notes of meeting of Chavez and members of bishops' committee, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 334)
    - Notebook 77. Daily notes on big union meeting at La Paz, 1975 Jun 13-19 (Box 14, Folder 335)
    - Notebook 78. Notes on part of Chavez 1,000 mile march, 1975 Aug (Box 14, Folder 336)
    - Notebook 79. Meetings of CALRA Board, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 337)
    - Notebook 80. Notes on implementation of California Agricultural Labor Relations Act (Box 14, Folder 338)
    - Notebook 81. Notes on meeting planning for farm worker elections, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 339)
    - Notebook 82. Notes of various UFW meetings, interview with Walter Kintz, notes on CALRB hearing, election results, 1975 Sep (Box 14, Folder 340)
    - Notebook 83. Notes on UFW complaints. Back of book: election results, 1975 Sep 24 (Box 14, Folder 341)
    - Notebook 84. Notes on hearings of Agricultural Labor Relations Board, 1975 Oct-Nov (Box 15, Folder 342)
    - Notebook 85. Notes for book picture captions. Draft of article on UFW and Third World, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 343)
  - 1976
    - Notebook 86. Local Sonoma County supervisorial campaign. Back of book: notes on State Legislature hearings, 1976 Mar-Apr (Box 15, Folder 344)
    - Notebook 87. Notes for speech at meeting of Gov. Brown and Chavez, 1976 Jul 12 (Box 15, Folder 345)
    - Notebook 88. Notes for Chavez re speech nominating Brown for president, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 346)
    - Notebook 89. Notes on seminar re movie making and script writing, and notes re potential movie on Chavez, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 347)
    - Notebook 90. Miscellaneous notes about union, elections, movie producer contacts, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 348)
    - Notebook 91. Notes on hearing by State Senate committee, events in Sonoma County, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 349)
    - Notebook 92. Notes on amendments to CALRA, making a movie, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 350)
    - Notebook 93. Notes on UFW convention and Sonoma county campaigns, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 351)
    - Notebook 94. Miscellaneous notes post book, including a historical perspective of Chavez and union, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 352)
    - Notebook 95. Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 353)
  - 1993-1994
    - Notebook 96. Questions for Rita Medina and Richard Chavez plus miscellaneous notes in preparation for second book on Cesar Chavez, 1993-94 (Box 16, Folder 354)
- Research Collection, 1959-1978; Series IV; 2.94; (7 boxes)
  Series IV, Research Collection, is organized into four subseries: Preliminary Research, Later Research, General Information, and Bracero 1965 Research. The subject files that comprise this series are filed in alphabetical order.
  - PRELIMINARY RESEARCH
    - File 1. Agribusiness Power, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 355)
    - File 2. Almaden Contract, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 356)
    - File 3. Arrests & Such Cases, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 357)
    - File 4. Bud Antle, Inc., n.d. (Box 17, Folder 358)
    - File 5. AWOC Radio Script #1, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 359)
    - File 6. AWOC, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 360-361)
    - File 7. Background Information, 1966, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 362-365)
    - File 8. Bad Working Conditions (Box 17, Folder 366)
    - File 9. Bibliography, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 367)
    - File 10. Birth Control & Other Items, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 368)
    - File 11. Boycott, 1969, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 369)
    - File 12. Brutality & Violence, 1969, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 370)
    - File 13. LeRoy Chatfield, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 371)
    - File 14. Cesar Chavez, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 372)
    - File 15. Cesar Chavez Appointment Book 1957, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 373-374)
    - File 16. Cesar Chavez Articles and Speeches, 1969, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 375-376)
    - File 17. Chavez Biography, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 377)
    - File 18. Cesar Chavez's Letters to Dolores Huerta, 1962-63, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 378)
    - File 19. Children of Migrants, 1969 Feb 23 (Box 18, Folder 379)
    - File 20. Christian Brothers, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 380)
    - File 21. Coachella Valley, 1969, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 381)
    - File 22. Credit Union, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 382)
    - File 23. Crusaders Against Agribusiness, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 383)
    - File 24. CSO, 1963, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 384-385)
    - File 25. DiGiorgio, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 386)
    - File 26. Jim Drake on History of NFWA, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 387)
    - File 27. "Events of Day" by Pete Velasco, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 388)
    - File 28. Farm Workers Association, 1962-63, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 389)
    - File 29. Fresno Free Speech Riot of 1910, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 390)
    - File 30. Grape Strike 1965-1970, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 391)
    - File 31. Grape Strike Letters '65-'66, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 392)
    - File 32. Growers, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 393)
    - File 33. John F. Henning, 1972 Jan 11 (Box 19, Folder 394)
    - File 34. Dolores Huerta Letters to Cesar Chavez, 1963, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 395)
    - File 35. Hunger, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 396)
    - File 36. InterHarvest Contract, 1970 Aug (Box 19, Folder 397)
    - File 37. Ill Fares the Land by Carey McWilliams (Box 19, Folder 398)
    - File 38. Larry Itliong, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 399)
    - File 39. Sen. Robert F. Kennedy, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 400)
    - File 40. La Follette, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 401)
    - File 41. Legal Actions, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 402)
    - File 42. Legislation, 1969 Mar-Apr (Box 19, Folder 403)
    - File 43. March to Sacramento, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 404)
    - File 44. Mechanization, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 405)
    - File 45. Medical Plan (UFWOC), 1969 Oct 1-15 (Box 19, Folder 406)
    - File 46. Migrants, 1969 Jan-Mar (Box 19, Folder 407)
    - File 47. Migrant Plight, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 408)
    - File 48. Militants, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 409)
    - File 49. NFWA, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 410)
    - File 50. NFWA: Service Center, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 411)
    - File 51. Opposition Arguments, 1968, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 412)
    - File 52. Pesticides, 1969 Mar 30 (Box 19, Folder 413)
    - File 53. Governor Ronald Reagan, 1968 Dec 3-9 (Box 19, Folder 414)
    - File 54. Dr. Jose Rizal, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 415)
    - File 55. Fred Ross Letters to Cesar Chavez, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 416)
    - File 56. Schenley, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 417)
    - File 57. Spanish, to be translated, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 418)
    - File 58. Strikes (Former History), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 419)
    - File 59. Subsidies, 1968 Nov 24 (Box 20, Folder 420)
    - File 60. Texas, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 421)
    - File 61. United Auto Workers, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 422)
    - File 62. UFWOC, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 423)
    - File 63. University of California, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 424)
    - File 64. Volunteers and Celebrities (Box 20, Folder 425)
    - File 65. War on Poverty Project, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 426)
    - File 66. "Wetbacks", 1968 Nov 24 (Box 20, Folder 427)
    - File 67. Press Clippings, 1969, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - LATER RESEARCH
    - Cesar Chavez Personal Papers
      - File 68. Articles by Cesar Chavez, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 429)
      - File 69. Chavez Family Homestead Documents, 1969, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 430)
      - File 70. Cesar Chavez Nominates Brown for President, 1976, 1976, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 431)
      - File 71. Cesar Chavez Statements, 1970-77, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 432)
      - File 72. Dogs, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 433)
      - File 73. Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 434)
    - Congressional Hearings
      - File 74. Congressional Hearings, 1968-72, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 435)
    - Official Farm Worker Materials
      - File 75. Corridos, 1962 Sep 25 (Box 20, Folder 436)
      - File 76. Legal, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 437)
      - File 77. UFW Conventions, 1975-77 (Box 20, Folder 438)
      - File 78. UFW Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 439)
      - File 79. UFW Internal Memos, 1975, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 440)
      - File 80. UFW Press Releases, 1970-78, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 441)
    - Subjects
      - File 81. AFL-CIO, 1975-76, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 442)
      - File 82. Boycott, 1970-76, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 443)
      - File 83. Illegal Aliens, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 444)
      - File 84. Teamsters, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 445)
      - File 85. Teamsters Rescinding Contracts, 1970-71 (Box 21, Folder 446)
    - Literature
      - File 86. Bibliography, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 447)
      - File 87. Cartoons, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 448)
      - File 88. Criticism of UFW, 1977, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 449)
      - File 89. Anne Draper, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 450)
      - File 90. Farm Worker Literature, 1970-78, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 451)
      - File 91. Opposition Literature, 1968-70, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 452)
      - File 92. Religious Community Support, 1965-78 (Box 21, Folder 453)
    - People
      - File 93. Richard Chavez, 1970 Jul 27 (Box 21, Folder 454)
      - File 94. Nan Freeman, 1972 Jan 25 (Box 21, Folder 455)
      - File 95. Larry Itliong, 1970 Jul 29 (Box 21, Folder 456)
      - File 96. Senator Robert F. Kennedy, 1968, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 457)
      - File 97. Coretta King, 1970 Dec 19 (Box 21, Folder 458)
      - File 98. Sidney Korshak, 1976 Aug 2 (Box 21, Folder 459)
      - File 99. Frank Little, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 460)
    - Growers
      - File 100. Bud Antle, 1970-71 (Box 21, Folder 461)
      - File 101. Growers, 1970, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 462)
      - File 102. Inter Harvest Inc, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 463)
  - GENERAL INFORMATION
    - File 103. Background Research (Box 21, Folder 464)
    - File 104. Law Enforcement Police Reports, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 465)
  - BRACERO 1965 COLLECTION
    - File 105. Department of Employment Farm Labor Scandals, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 466)
    - File 106. Death Throes of PL 78, 1964-65 (Box 22, Folder 467)
    - File 107. California Department of Labor, 1963-65 (Box 22, Folder 468)
    - File 108. California Labor Department Activities, 1962-65 (Box 22, Folder 469)
    - File 109. Fields of Bondage, 1963 May 1 (Box 22, Folder 470)
    - File 110. Farm Labor Recruitment, 1964 Oct (Box 22, Folder 471)
    - File 111. Recruitment Supplemental Report, 1964 Dec (Box 22, Folder 472)
    - File 112. Equal Rights for Farm Labor, 1964 Dec (Box 22, Folder 473)
    - File 113. "Slaves for Rent", 1965 May (Box 22, Folder 474)
    - File 114. California Personnel Board Appeal Hearing, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 475-477)
- News Clippings, 1961-1996; Series V; 1.68; (5 boxes)
  Series V, News Clippings, is arranged in chronological order. The Levy inventory lists the clippings individually, and their numbers are used here for the large 1973 clippings file. The UFW Collected Clipping Sheets appear at the end of the series and are arranged in a separate chronological order.
  - Clippings Prior to 1969, 1961-68, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 478)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folder 946
  - 1969 Clippings, 1969, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 479-482)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folder 947
  - 1970 Clippings, 1970, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 483-490)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folders 948-950 and broadside folder 978
  - 1971 Clippings, 1971, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 491-493)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folder 951
  - 1972 Clippings, 1972, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 494-496)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folder 952
  - 1973 Clippings: clipping numbers 823 to 1124, 1973, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 497-501)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folder 953 and broadside folder 979
  - 1973 Clippings: clipping numbers 1125 to 1624, 1973, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 502-510)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folders 954-956 and broadside folder 980
  - 1974 Clippings, 1974, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 511-513)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folder 957
  - 1975 Clippings, 1975, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 514)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 50, folder 958
  - 1976-1996 Clippings, 1976-96, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 515)
    Stored also in: Oversize box 51, folder 959